What happened?
She drank too much.
I tore it.
What happened at the banquet yesterday?
You told me
to take orders for the escort agency.
But I couldn't fit in at all yesterday.
Zhang Xiayun
is a real beauty,
while I
am a real ugly.
She's better than me in everything.
I can't hold back
a girl who wants to be a phoenix.
So you've stuck it?
Yes.
How can I divorce him without a divorce paper?
We're about to break up.
He insisted that
I promised to help him with the speech yesterday.
He's dreaming.
No.
You have to prepare for the final interview with him.
You must shine in front of Zhang Xi Yun.
This is called tit for tat.
Why are you the only one who is not happy?
But
You don't mean
to give up, do you?
Give up?
I will give up?
Su Yuejiao will never give up.
That's right.
Su's Escort Agency
is always with the escort.
So I'll keep this for you first.
In case you tear it again.
Yesterday,
you favored Cheng Qi at the banquet.
Today,
the complaint was brought to me.
It was my negligence.
I didn't let Mr. Ling win the competition.
I'll be more careful
in the final.
You can fool Qi Jia with that,
but not me.
I'm sorry.
Why?
I know I was wrong.
I don't care about the winner.
They're all pawns.
Whoever you pick,
you must control them
and handle the consequences.
Don't let me clean up your mess.
Yes.
The Queen has assigned Yue Shangzhi
to attend the final.
So whatever you want to do,
you must do it cleanly.
Am I clear enough?
Yes.
My Lady,
did the Lord take out his anger on you?
Not only not,
he even gave me a sword.
Tang Xin's music is ready.
Faca,
you're in charge of controlling the rhythm and brightness of the shadow.
Qian,
the props of the scenery are up to you.
Okay.
Gong Xi,
you help Qian.
Okay, my son-in-law.
Jiao.
You just play yourself.
This is your story.
I can't believe my boss agreed.
He's even full of fighting spirit.
Why is mine so thick?
Today is the final of the Starry Sky Literary Awards.
Not only do we have several literary masters participating in the selection,
but also Mr. Yue from the Ministry of Rites overseeing the event.
I'm sure the competition will be spectacular.
The first round of the final
the first round,
the keywords are
heart, cloud, flower, and moon.
The heart, after drawing lots,
will be started by Mr. Cheng.
Please.
I remember the first time I met you,
you were wearing a double-layered silk dress.
I am like a magnetized needle,
pointing to the south.
The heart of a guest competes with the sun and moon,
anticipating the journey.
If I don't write poetry for a day,
my heart becomes like a dry well.
The shadow is upright because it is straight.
The heart is strong and lazy to hide its edge.
Flowers never end, the moon is endless.
Two hearts are the same.
Cloud.
The bright moon idly leans by the water.
White clouds invite guests to climb higher.
The autumn wind rises, and the white clouds fly.
The grass and trees turn yellow, and the wild geese return south.
Layer upon layer of peach and plum blossoms on the mountain.
The smoke and fire in the clouds are the homes of people.
Hua.
The flower does not bloom with the hundred flowers.
Standing alone in the sparse fence, its charm is endless.
How can one bear to see the painting change its colors?
How can one allow the rivers and mountains to turn to ashes?
The jade bowl is cold with dew,
The fragrance of snow permeates the gauze.
The hall is fragrant with incense.
The waist is slim and delicate.
What a talent!
The clear and elegant temperament is suitable for a guest.
The tranquil and silent temperament is suitable for a king.
The moon.
The moon is so beautiful that it brings a different atmosphere.
The moon is so precious that it is worth a fortune.
The moon is so kind that it knows my feelings.
I can't bear to see the moon at its fullest tonight.
Who is as affectionate as the moon of the South Mountain?
It parts the evening clouds on purpose.
Who pushed the bright moon
up into the sky?
The moonlight is like water after parting.
I miss you every night.
The moon accompanies me on my journey.
Its light falls on my quilt in a strange land.
The first round of the flying flower order ends here.
It's a great honor to see all the talented individuals
perform so wonderfully.
The results are out.
The talents who have entered the middle round are
Ling Feng, Mr. Ling,
Cheng Qi, Mr. Cheng,
Xin Bufang, Mr. Xin.
Please take a break.
We will draw lots to determine the order for the next round.
Lord Yue, Miss Zhang,
I am willing to go first in this round,
to give other talents more time to prepare.
Mr. Ling, you are so kind.
Mr. Ling, you volunteer to go first.
Please get ready, Mr. Ling.
He did it on purpose.
It's all acting.
He's not novel.
Although it's all acting,
we have a trump card.
What's the trump card?
Why don't I know?
Jiao, don't think about it.
Later,
just pretend it's your dream
to meet your mother.
Good, good.
Very good.
It's beautiful,
but lacks power.
Next, please welcome Cheng Qi.
Mr. Cheng.
Go for it, my son-in-law!
Mom,
is this the City of Diamond?
It's different from Yunjing.
Isn't it beautiful?
Are you escorts from Yunjing?
You must be tired.
Mom,
their accent is so strange.
They are
Langyue people doing business in the Yun State.
So does he find our accent
strange too?
No, no,
your accent is very pleasant.
Hope everything goes well for you here.
Jiao,
I hid a chicken leg in the cart.
Go find it.
Mom, you always do this.
You always tell me after I'm full.
Su's Escort Agency.
We'll protect the goods with our lives.
Mom, the drumstick is so delicious.
I'm leaving.
Jiao,
you should continue your journey
and see all the beauty of the Yun State for me.
Mom!
Mom,
I've seen it for you.
The Yun State is becoming more and more beautiful.
That's great.
Immersed in it.
Who is Cheng Qi?
The son of the deputy of Ning'an County.
According to the scores of all the guests,
the champion of this Star Conference is
Cheng Qi.
I thought he was extraordinary from the first round.
He deserves to be the champion.
Yeah.
Congratulations!
I'll always remember
your recognition.
Cloud Book Bureau and Huayue Tower
will join forces with the top scholar
to add luster to the prosperous Yun State.
My lord, are we still going according to the plan?
Of course.
My lord,
we'll go back and prepare.
Go.
Okay.
Let's go, Qianzhi.
Aren't we waiting for Cheng Qi?
Didn't we want to give him a surprise?
Of course, we should let them be alone at this time.
Right, right.
Let's go, go home.
My father has prepared a banquet at home to celebrate.
Since the Grand Preceptor has invited,
we must attend.
Miss Zhang,
I need to inform my family.
I've already sent someone to inform them.
I thought you would want to discuss the follow-up of the book
and the recitation meeting.
Could it be that the top scholar
intends to make a living in the escort agency for a lifetime?
If so, I'll bother you.
Why are you still here, Mr. Su?
Mr. Cheng went to the banquet with my lady.
A banquet?
And he didn't even tell me.
Eat.
He just won the top of the Star Cloud Competition and disappeared.
It makes sense.
The food at the Grand Preceptor's Mansion
is much better than ours.
Don't wait.
Let's eat.
The food at home is not good.
You don't eat it.
You can't keep your people,
why are you mad at me?
I just don't like you today.
You have such a bad temper.
If I were Cheng Qi, I wouldn't return either.
Say that again.
I...
Can you stop quarreling all day?
His Majesty is quite interested in this.
He believes that all of you
are the future of our nation's literary scene.
If you enter the court,
you will make a great contribution.
As the Grand Preceptor,
you are willing to promote us.
We are so lucky.
We will respect you
and live up to your expectations.
Cheng Qi.
Yes.
I remember your father was sidelined.
Now he is just a county sheriff.
If you become an official,
you'll bring honor to your family.
My Lord,
I just like writing poems.
I don't want to be an official.
Really?
Mr. Cheng is unrestrained and free.
With your talent, you may
bring fortune to the people of the Yun State.
If so,
then don't force yourself.
Thank you for your appreciation.
Thank you for your compliment.
Come on.
Let's drink together.
Burn the bridge after crossing it.
You just finished acting,
and then
you ran away with him.
Jiaojiao.
It's a banquet hosted by the Grand Preceptor, not a private meeting.
Is it necessary to be so angry?
Who said it's because of Cheng Qi?
Who mentioned Cheng Qi?
You're admitting it yourself.
Where he wants to go,
who he wants to stay with,
has nothing to do with me.
Exactly.
He won the top of the Xingyun competition.
You're about to take over as the Grand Secretariat.
Once you two separate,
of course, there's no connection.
Xin,
you've hit him
and smashed things.
Are you still mad?
Instead of being upset and making guesses,
you'd better ask him directly
if he wants to stay or go.
How do I ask him?
You're leaving already?
Miss Zhang,
thanks for the help at the Starry Night.
I should be grateful.
How do you plan to thank me?
These are
the lyrics and expanded scripts for my final trial.
I'll give them to you.
These papers
are quite valuable now.
Are you trying to do business with me?
They are valuable because of you.
If you stay in Yunjing in the future,
please help me.
Don't worry.
I won't forget your contribution.
Are you in such a hurry to leave
because of your wife?
I'm sorry to make you laugh.
She is actually
a very considerate woman,
not as the rumors say.
You are really a couple of lovebirds.
My wife and I have promised to be together
until old age, naturally hoping to help each other.
When true is false, false is true.
It seems that Mr. Cheng
has made a fake play real.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
You and Su
got married by contract.
You don't have to be surprised.
The leader of Xingyun,
wouldn't I have investigated his background?
Miss Zhang,
as a live-in son-in-law,
if I don't go back,
I'll be kicked out of the house.
Don't worry.
You can live in my villa.
I'm afraid to bother you.
I'll take my leave.
Miss,
I did see the divorce paper from Tang Xin.
But why is Cheng Qi...
Then we can push them
to divorce.
It's like a trap.
I didn't dare to eat anything.
Will there be nothing to eat when we get back?
It won't be that bad.
They will leave some for us.
Let's go.
After the competition,
I was invited to the Grand Preceptor's Mansion.
It took me a while to sneak out.
I've flattered you enough for a lifetime.
Are you mad at me?
My hands are numb.
Why don't you go back to sleep?
I'm waiting for you.
Waiting for me?
Aren't you mad at me?
Why would I be mad?
What if I become a successful person
and never come back?
Are you that kind of person?
No.
But I'm hungry.
Can I have
this chicken leg?
No.
Congratulations, son-in-law,
on topping the imperial examination.
We've been discussing for a while
and decided to wait for you to come back
to celebrate your success.
You've made a great achievement!
You're the top scholar!
What a happy family!
You're the best!
Delicious!
A family
should be together.
Come on.
Cheng Qi,
you're the best today,
and come out on top?
Grandpa,
our son-in-law has always been great.
I didn't realize it before,
but today, Cheng Qi really
surprised us all.
Of course.
Although he's still
a bit behind me.
Cheng Qi,
I want to toast you separately
Thank you for taking care of Jiaojiao.
Jiaojiao's
parents died early,
and she's been spoiled by me.
She's domineering, arrogant,
and does things without thinking of the consequences,
like a boy.
Thank you for your understanding and tolerance.
At the same time,
welcome to our big family.
Thank you, Grandpa.
I toast to you, Grandpa.
Good.
Come on.
I'll join you.
Then let's drink together.
Okay.
Then let's do it together.
Together, together.
Let's toast.
Boss, you drink water so happily.
Come on.
The straw man's arm
has been cut off.
Instead of guessing and getting upset,
you might as well ask him directly
if he wants to stay or go.
[She still cares about the divorce papers.]
[I need to hurry up.]
I'm going back to Ning'an in a few days.
You won the top scholar,
to confront my parents?
I'm buying a house in the capital.
So,
I have to go back and tell them.
Looks like
you're not coming back.
Should I buy the house
near the agency?
I can come back for dinner.
You're still thinking about dinner
Cheng Qi,
how could you do that?
As you wish.
It seems she agreed.
It's a bit cold today.
I heard the fur in Langyue is good.
I'll buy a big one later.
He's not content with sleeping on the ground.
He doesn't want to stay at all.
Heartless,
cold-hearted.
He doesn't like me at all.
What's the point of asking?